Guide to the Montana Carey Land Act Board records 1897-1962
Montana Historical Society Research Center
- Reports (at 31:1-1)
  - Correspondence, Images of Swift Dam Area After June 1964 Floods, State Examiner Report, Water Irrigation Project/Reports, Maps, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, Boundaries, Maps, Lands Loaned, Rules and Regulations, Preliminary Report on the Crow Creek Irrigation Project, Purchased Lands, Statement Presented to Calvin Coolidge-Aug 30, 1927 Concerning Columbia River Basin, 1919-1927 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Clippings, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Valier Project: Applications for Entry, No. 155-275, 1909-1912 (Box-folder 14/4-17)
  - Valier Project: Applications for Entry, No. 276-460, circa 1912-1916 (Box-folder Box 15 (18 folders))
  - Valier Project: Applications for Entry, No. 470 – 649., circa 1916-1920 (Box-folder Box 16 (18 folders))
  - Valier Project: Applications for Entry, No. 650-799, circa 1918-1942 (Box-folder Box 17 (20 folders)